아침에 이메일을
받았는데 너무 흥분돼
So, I got the craziest
e-mail this morning.
이런 말해서 미안하지만
I don't mean to burst
your bubble, dude,
성기확대제는 효과 없어
but those penile enlargement
pills do not work.
그건 나도 알아
Believe me, I know.
스티븐 호킹네 비서가
보낸 이메일이었어
The e-mail I got was
from the office of
Stephen Hawking.
- 정말?
- 왜?
- You're kidding.
- Why?
몇 주 동안 여기서
강의를 한다는데
He's coming to the university
for a couple weeks to lecture,
휠체어 장비를 관리할
엔지니어가 필요하대
and he's looking for an
engineer to help maintain
the equipment on his wheelchair.
좋겠다
That's amazing.
피트크루가 되는거네
You'll be like his pit crew.
경고하자면
A word of caution:
I would not do
스티븐 호킹 앞에서
성대모사는 자제해줘
your Stephen Hawking
impression in front of him.
맞아
(in Stephen Hawking's voice):
You're right.
그건 무례하게
보일 수 있겠군
I suppose that could be
considered offensive.
쉘든이 식겁하겠다
Boy, Sheldon's going
to freak out.
호킹을 거의 숭배하잖아
Yeah, he worships Hawking.
쉘든도 같이
데리고 갈 생각이야
I was actually thinking
about bringing him along
직접 만나게 해주고 싶어
when I go over there so
he can meet the great man.
좋은 일 하네
That's really nice
of you, Howard.
별 거 아냐
It's no big deal.
호킹한테도 접근 금지
명령을 받겠군
Boy, a restraining order
from Stephen Hawking.
컬렉션에 추가하면 되겠네
It'll look so nice next to
the ones he's already got
레너드 니모이, 칼 세이건,
스탠 리에 이어
from Leonard Nimoy,
Carl Sagan and Stan Lee.
레너드, 이거 기억나?
Leonard, do you recall
내가 이렇게 말했지
when I said that I was going
힉스 입자에 대한
개념을 재정립하겠다고
to revolutionize
humanity's understanding
of the Higgs boson particle,
and you said,
넌 새벽 2시라며
꺼지라고 했잖아
"Sheldon, it's 2:00 a.m.,
get out of my bedroom"?
10시간 전이잖아
Like it was ten hours ago.
어떻게 됐어?
What about it?
어쩌면 해낸 것 같아
Well, I believe I've done it.
겸손한 척하려고
'어쩌면'이라고 표현했지만
And I'm only saying "believe"
to sound modest,
실제로 해냈어
because, sweet Sam Houston,
I did it.
정말?
대단하다
Really?
That's incredible. Oh, here.
계산 좀 보여줘
Break out the math.
어디 보자
Oh, okay, let me see this.
여기 있는 입자가 시간의
흐름에 따라 이동한다 치자
All right, so
this particle here
is the boson moving
forward in time.
하워드, 넌 먼저 먹어
Now, I was thinking...
Howard, you go ahead and eat.
어차피 이해 못하잖아
This isn't going to make
any sense to you.
쉘든, 난 기초저인
물리학 지식은 갖췄어
Sheldon, I have a working
understanding of physics.
계속 기초를 다지도록
Yeah, good for you,
and don't stop working on it.
이래도 그 분
얘기 꺼낼거야?
Are you still
going to tell him
about you-know-who?
Yep.
이래도 소개해주려고?
Are you still going
to introduce him?
절대 그럴 수는 없지
Not on your life.
♪ Our whole universe was
in a hot, dense state ♪
♪ Then nearly 14 billion years
ago expansion started... Wait! ♪
♪ The Earth began to cool ♪
♪ The autotrophs began to drool,
Neanderthals developed tools ♪
♪ We built the Wall ♪
♪ We built the pyramids ♪
♪ Math, Science, History,
unraveling the mystery ♪
♪ That all started
with a big bang ♪
♪ Bang! ♪
DC 기타 미국드라마 갤러리
The Big Bang Theory 5x21
The Hawking Excitation
Original Air Date on April 5, 2012
자막 공대언니
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
제발, 제발, 제발
Please, please, please
호킹을 만나게 해줘
let me meet Hawking.
안 된다고
I told you, no.
미안하다고 했잖아
But I said I'm sorry.
아니, 사과하면
달라지냐고 물었지
No, you said, "Would it help
if I said I'm sorry?"
그리고 넌 답을
주지 않았어
And you never answered me.
이제 누가 사과해야
되는 상황일까?
So who owes whom an apology now?
너처럼 잘난 체만
하는 놈한테
Sheldon,
you're a condescending jerk.
뭐하러 호의를 베풀겠어?
Why on earth would I want
to do something nice for you?
Um...
유대교 천국에 가기 위해?
to go to Jewish heaven?
유대교에서는
천국을 믿지 않아
Jews don't have heaven.
그럼 지옥을 피하기 위해?
Then to avoid Jewish hell?
우리 엄마 못 봤어?
Have you met my mother?
같이 사는 것
자체가 지옥이야
I live in Jewish hell.
하워드, 제발
Howard, please.
스티븐 호킹이잖아
This is Stephen Hawking.
지적 능력이 그나마
비슷한 사람이라고
Perhaps my only
intellectual equal.
무슨 헛소리야
(chuckling)
Oh, you can't be serious.
내 입장을 좀 생각해줘
Try to put yourself
in my place.
지구 상의 유일한
인간이라고 상상해봐
Imagine you're the
sole human being
주변에는 멍멍이밖에 없지
living on a planet populated
with nothing but dogs.
그러던 어느 날
And then it turns out
같은 종족을
발견하는 거야
there's another human being.
그러니까
Hang on.
다른 사람들을
개 취급하는 건가?
Are you saying
the rest of us are dogs?
그래, 오해의
소지가 좀 있군
Okay, I can see you're going
to take this the wrong way.
다시 해볼게
Let me try again.
지구 상의 유일한
인간이라고 상상해봐
Imagine you're the
sole human being
주변에는 침팬지밖에 없어
living on a planet populated
with nothing but chimps.
좀 나가줄래
Get out of my lab.
개보다는 훨씬 똑똑하다고
Oh, now they're so much smarter
than dogs.
자전거 타는 거 못 봤어?
Have you seen them
on those little bicycles?
꺼져
Get out.
돌고래는 어때?
How about dolphins?
꺼지라고
Out!
호킹은 잘 만났어?
So, come on, how was
the first day with Hawking?
너무 좋았어
It was great.
영화 얘기도 나누고
We talked about movies...
(groans): Oh...
카드 마술도 보여주고
I showed him some card tricks...
Oh!
새 책도 미리 읽게 해주더라
He even let me read a couple
pages from his new book.
(groans): Oh!
무슨 문제니, 친구야?
Something got
you down there, bunky?
하워드, 제발,
부탁할게
Howard, please,
I'm begging you.
라지, 넌 우리
과거를 잘 알지
Raj,
you're our group historian.
쉘든이 이렇게
부탁한 적이 있나?
Has Sheldon ever begged before?
세 번 있었어
Three times.
폭스 방송사에 '파이어플라이'를
캔슬하지 말라하고
He begged the Fox network
not to cancel Firefly.
TNT에는 '바빌론 5'를
캔슬하라고 했고
He begged
the TNT network
to cancel Babylon 5.
신년 행사에서
식중독 걸렸을 때는
And when he got food poisoning
at the Rose Bowl Parade,
믿지도 않는 신한테
빨리 끝내달라고 빌었지
he begged a deity
he doesn't believe in
to end his life quickly.
호킹이 나한테
어떤 존재인지 알아?
Do you understand how
important Hawking is to me?
6살 때는
When I was six years old,
호킹 변장을 하고
할로윈을 보냈어
I dressed up as
him for Halloween.
에이 설마
You're kidding.
아빠의 사무실 의자에
말하는 장난감을 달고
No, sir, no, I took
my dad's desk chair,
attached a Speak
& Spell to it
동생이 밀어주는 동안
캔디를 받았지
and made my sister push
me up and down the block
to trick or treat.
사람들은 내가
R2-D2인 줄 알았지만
Granted most people
thought I was R2-D2,
그래도 캔디는 많이 받았어
but still, I got a lot of candy.
영어 '노'의
의미를 잘 모르나보네
You don't seem
to be understanding
the English word "no."
다른 언어로 해볼게
Maybe a different language
will help.
러시아어, nyet
Russian: nyet.
중국어, bu
Chinese: bu.
일어, iie
Japanese: iie.
클링곤, qo'
Klingon: qo'.
아스키 코드
0110111001101111
Binary coded Ascii:
0110111001101111.
그게 아니라
01100111
It's actually 01100111.
No!
내 자신을
위한 부탁이 아냐
I'm not asking for me,
호킹을 위한 거지
I'm asking for Hawking.
갱스터 말투로 해볼게,
헬 노
Let me try gansta:
Hells naw.
이러면 어때?
Okay, look, how about this?
내가 쓴 힉스 입자
논문을 전해줘
Just give him my paper
on the Higgs boson.
얼마나 기발한지
깨달으면 먼저 연락하겠지
If he sees the
incredible breakthrough
I've made, he'll
reach out to me.
안 그러면?
What if he doesn't?
연락할거야,
진짜 똑똑하거든
He will; he's really smart.
흥미로운 제안이군
That's an interesting idea.
친구들이랑 상의할
시간이 좀 필요해
Why don't you give me
a minute to talk it over
with my friends?
- 난 어떻게 할까?
- 자리를 피해줘
- How do I do that?
- You walk away.
자리 피하는 중
Walking away.
완전 꽉 잡고 있네
You do realize
you own his ass right now.
알아
I do.
뭐든 시킬 수 있어
You can make him
do anything you want.
얼마나 더 장난을
쳐야할지 고민이야
Yeah, I know, I'm just trying
to figure out
how much I want to punish him.
너무 심하게 하지는 마
Well, don't be too mean.
얘들아
SHELDON:
Hey, fellas,
아이스티 만드려는데
마실 사람 있어?
I'm thinking about making some
freshly brewed iced tea
if anyone would like some.
난 좋지
I wouldn't mind a glass.
너한테 한 말이 아냐
I wasn't talking to you.
무릎이 닳도록
빌게 만들어
Bring him to his bony knees.
쉘든, 다시 와도 돼
Sheldon, come on back.
Yes, yes.
결정했어?
What did you decide?
논문을 전해줄게
I'll give your paper
to Professor Hawking.
고마워
Great, thank you!
잘 됐다
Oh, that's terrific!
대신 네가 해야할 일이 있어
But in exchange, I'd like you
to do a few things for me.
무슨 일인데?
What kinds of things?
헤라클레스의 12 가지
노동에 대해 알아?
Are you familiar
with the 12 labors of Hercules?
물론이지
Of course.
그보다는 힘들 거야
You should be so lucky.
All right.
무엇부터 할까?
What would you like me
to do first?
벨트 버클부터
닦아주면 좋겠네
Well, I thought
I'd start you off
by polishing my belt buckles.
Oh.
그러지 뭐
By all means.
어릴 때 할머니 심부름으로
은식기를 닦았었지
When I was a boy, I would
polish my Mee-Maw's silver.
할머니는 오클라호마에서
살던 얘기를 해주셨어
And she would entertain me
with stories
about growing up in Oklahoma.
재밌는 분이셔
Interesting woman.
한번은 소스 그릇으로
프레리도그를 죽였대
She once killed a prairie dog
with a gravy boat.
그렇군
That's nice.
(exhales)
벨트 버클이 정말 많네
That's a lot of belt buckles.
재밌는 건
벨트는 하냐
Funny thing is,
I only have one belt.
그럼 시작하도록 해
Anyway, I'll let
you get started.
참고로
Oh, by the way,
물자국처럼 보이는 건
the little marks, uh,
that look like water spots--
소변기를 너무
가까이 사용해서
I tend to stand too close
to the urinal, so...
뭔가가 튀어서
생긴 자국이야
...what you're seeing there
is splash back.
벨트 버클에 오줌을?
You make sissy
on your belt buckles?
할머니가 쓰던 포크에는
그런 자국 없었는데
Mee-Maw's forks never had that.
자외선 조사등으로
확인해봐
Here is a black light
to check them.
마음의 평안을 위해
And for your own peace of mind,
천장이나 다른 곳은
안 비추는게 좋아
you might not want to shine that
around the rest of the room.
쉘든, 정말 대단하다
Sheldon, these look great.
내 아름다운 보석을
장식할 아름다운 왕관이군
They're like
magnificent little crowns
to hang over
my magnificent little jewels.
뭘 했길래
이렇게 반짝이지?
How'd you get them so shiny?
터틀왁스를 썼어
Oh, I-I buffed them
with Turtle Wax.
자동차 부품 가게
아저씨가 그러는데
The man down at Pep Boys
says from now on,
오줌이 튀겨도
굴러떨어질 거래
the urine should just bead up
and roll right off.
애썼네
Way to go the extra mile.
할머니가
자랑스러워 하겠다
Your Mee-Maw would be proud.
할머니가 알면 안돼
My Mee-Maw
must never know of this.
이제 논문을 전해줄래?
Now will you give
Professor Hawking my paper?
이런, 아직은 안돼
Oh, my dear boy, no.
Okay.
Next,
이건 섹시한
프랑스 하녀 복장이야
this is
a sexy French maid costume
베르나데트를
입히려고 샀지
I bought for Bernadette.
분위기도 띄우고
I thought it might
spice things up
동시에 청소도 좀 시키려고
and get her to dust
my room at the same time,
내 착각이였지만
but I was wrong
and really wrong.
반품해달라고?
And you want me to
return it for you?
아이고, 귀여운 것
No, no, no, mon petit cherie.
뭘 쳐다봐?
What are you all staring at?
스티븐 호킹이랑
만나려는 사람 처음 보시나?
You ever seen a man try
to get a meeting
with Stephen Hawking before?
(laughter)
Hey.
Hello.
토요일 밤 아니잖아
It's not Saturday night.
왠 빨래야?
Why are you doing
your laundry?
내 세탁물이 아냐
This is not
my laundry.
에이미 옷인가?
Wow, are these Amy's?
저질스러운 스타일이네
Kind of trashy-- good for her.
하워드 옷이야
Those are Howard's.
Ugh...
왜 하워드 속옷을 빨아?
Why are you washing
Howard's man panties?
안 그러면
Because if I don't,
스티븐 호킹한테
내 논문을 안 보여준대
he won't give my paper
to Stephen Hawking.
유명한 물리학자야
- He's a famous physicist.
- Yeah, yeah,
알아, 휄체어에 앉아
시간을 발명한 사람이잖아
I know, he's the wheelchair dude
who invented time.
비슷하긴 하네
That's close enough.
그냥 하워드한테
소개해달라고 하면 안돼?
I don't understand,
why doesn't Howard
just introduce you to the guy?
내가 잘난 척 해서
벌 주는 거야
Because he's punishing me for
being a "condescending jerk."
내가 거만하다고 생각해?
You don't think
I'm condescending, do you?
좀 그렇지
Well, kind of...
미안, 거만하다의 뜻은...
Oh, I'm sorry,
condescending means...
뭔지 알거든
I know what it means.
남의 잘못을 지적하고
무시하니까 맞는 말이지
And yes,
you love correcting people
and putting them down.
반대로
Au contraire.
남의 잘못을 지적하는건
상대방을 돕는 일이야
When I correct people
I am raising them up.
너도 많은 도움을 받았지
You should know, I do it
for you more than anyone.
우월함을 느끼려고
하는 거잖아
Come on, you do it
to feel superior.
지적할 때마다
눈이 반짝이던데
I see that twinkle in your eye
누군가 'whom' 대신
'who'를 쓰거나
when someone says "who"
instead of "whom"
달도 행성이라 알고 있거나
or thinks the moon is a planet.
돈키호테가 호테라는 당나귀에
관한 책이라고 생각하기도 했지
Or Don Quixote is a book
about a donkey named Hotay.
거봐
See,
또 반짝이네
there it is,
there's that twinkle.
어쩔 수 없어
Well, I can't help it.
나도 모르게 하는 거야
That's an involuntary twinkle.
무슨 말을 듣고 싶니?
What do you want me
to tell you, Sheldon?
하워드가 이유 없이
못되게 구는 거라고 말해줘
I want you to tell me
that Howard is being mean to me
for no reason.
하워드가 이유 없이
못되게 굴고 있어
Fine, Howard is being mean
to you for no reason.
그럴 줄 알았다
I knew it.
(groans)
무슨 일이야?
What's the matter?
자러 오는 날에는
Every time I spend the night,
어머님이 엉덩이를 치면서
'화이팅'이라고 외치잖아
your mom slaps me on the behind
and says, "Go get 'em."
엄마 잘못이 아냐
It's not her fault.
호르몬 대체
치료를 받고 있어
She's getting
hormone replacement therapy.
엄마도 참기 어려울 거야
Makes her crazy horny.
쉘든한테 하녀 옷을
입힌 것 좀 봐봐
Check this out,
I got Sheldon
to wear the French
maid's costume.
저런
Oh, my God,
that's terrible.
너도 입을 기회 있었잖아
Hey, I gave you
first crack at it.
왜 그러는 거야?
Why are you doing that?
너무 못됐다
You're being mean to him.
쉘든도 항상 그러는걸
He's mean to me all the time.
박사 학위 없다고
놀리는거 들었잖아
You've heard him tease me
about not having a doctorate.
놀림 당하기 싫으면
너도 따면 되지
If you don't want
to get teased about that,
get a doctorate.
나도 있는데 좋거든
I have one; they're great.
이 놈은 날 괴롭히잖아
Oh, come on, the
man torments me.
똑같이 당하게
하는 것 뿐이야
I'm just letting him have
a little taste
of his own medicine.
상황이 다르잖아
It's not the same thing.
쉘든은 자기가 언제
나쁜 행동을 하는지 몰라
Sheldon doesn't know
when he's being mean
잘못을 인식 못하는
뇌 구조를 갖고 있어
because the part of his brain
that should know
is getting a wedgie
from the rest of his brain.
그럼 몇 가지만 더 시키고
Fine, I'll just make him do
a couple more things,
그만할게
then I'll stop.
아니, 지금 그만해
No, you have to stop now.
베르나데트, 내일 같이
쇼핑하기로 했지
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Bernadette, I want to remind you,
you promised to take me
dress shopping tomorrow!
젠장
Oh, damn.
죄송한데
못 가게 됐어요
I'm sorry,
I can't make it,
쉘든이 대신 간대요
but Sheldon's going
to go with you!
이번이 마지막이야
And that's the last thing
you do to him.
쉘든
MRS. WOLOWITZ:
Sheldon!
도와줘
I need your help!
무슨 일이세요?
What is it now, Mrs. Wolowitz?
이 드레스 때문에
It's this dress!
앞을 넣으면 뒤가 터져
When I put my front in,
my back pops out!
뒤를 넣으면
앞이 튀어나오고
When I put my back in,
my front pops out!
욕조에 개 두 마리를
씻기는 것만큼 힘들어
It's like trying to keep
two dogs in a bathtub!
제가 어떻게 하면 될까요?
What do you want me to do?
팀워크가 필요해
We're gonna have
to work as a team!
들어와서 한 덩어리
잡고 쑤셔넣어
Get in here, grab a handful,
and start stuffing!
어떻게 해야되는지 모르겠어요
SHELDON:
I'm not sure how to do this.
침낭을 말아
넣는다고 생각해봐
It's easy, just pretend you're
putting away a sleeping bag.
침난은 이렇게
땀을 흘리지 않지만
Sleeping bags don't usually
sweat this much, but okay.
이제 지퍼를 올려봐
Now zip me up.
더 조이면 다이아몬드로
변할지도 몰라요
Oh, if we squeeze
you any tighter,
you may turn
into a diamond.
그래, 이건 무리다
You're right,
who am I kidding?
젊은 시절에는
잘 나갔어
You should have seen me
when I was young, Sheldon.
날 쫓아다니던 놈들이
캔디를 갖다 바쳤지
The fellas used to line up
and bring me boxes of candy.
왜 다 먹어치웠을까?
Why did I eat it all?!
날 안아줄래?
Would you hold me?
이런, 그닥 내키지 않는데...
Oh... no, you know, I'm not
really the holding kind of...
Oh!
방금 생각났는데
Oh, guys, I just remembered.
호킹 기념품을 갖고 왔어
I got you
some Hawking souvenirs.
뭔데?
What are these?
휠체어 부품 좀 챙겨왔지
Gears and springs
from his wheelchair.
멋지지?
Pretty cool, huh?
엄청나다
Wow, that's amazing.
전동부를 손 봤는데
I made an adjustment
on the motor drive
다시 합쳐 놓을때
and when I was putting it
back together
어디에 끼워 맞춰야
하는지 모르겠더라
I could not for the life of me
figure out where they went.
다했다
(sighs)
I did it.
가게를 세 군데나 들리고
Had to go
to three clothing stores,
너네 엄마를 덮을
드레스를 드디어 찾았어
but we finally found a dress
that could envelop your mother.
앨터디너에 있는
자동차 커버 가게를 알려줄걸
I should have sent you
to the custom car cover place
in Altadena.
엄마 사이즈가
등록되어 있거든
They have her pattern on file.
(laughs)
재밌네
Humorous.
이제 내 논문을
호킹한테 전해줄래?
Now will you
please present
my paper
to Professor Hawking?
모르겠다
I don't know.
제발 부탁이야
Oh, for heaven's sake.
빨래도 해주고,
버클에 오줌을 닦아내고
I did your laundry, I pee-pee-
proofed your belt buckles,
너네 엄마 젖통을
받쳐주다가 손목도 삐었어
I, I even sprained
my wrist helping
your mother lift her bosom.
알겠어
All right, Sheldon,
마지막으로 도와줘
there's only one thing left
I want you to do.
걱정 마,
쉬운 일이야
Don't worry, it's an easy one.
Okay.
날 칭찬해줘
Give me a compliment.
그래
Fine.
넌 손이 매우 작아
You have very tiny hands.
아니, 내 직업에 대해
No... about my job.
내 일은 잘 한다고 듣고 싶어
I want you to tell me
I'm good at what I do.
당연히 잘하고 있지
You're obviously good
at what you do.
그럼 왜 날 그렇게 까대?
Well, then why are you
always ripping on me?
왜 그러는지 알겠다
Oh, I understand
the confusion.
네가 일을 못 한다고
한 적은 없어
I have never said that you are
not good at what you do.
네가 하는 일이
가치가 없는 거지
It's just that what you do
is not worth doing.
나한테 한 말에
비하면 칭찬이네
It's nicer than anything
he's ever said to me.
이 정도로 만족해라
I'd take it and run.
고마워, 쉘든
Thank you, Sheldon.
이제 내 논문을
전해줄 수 있지?
Now will you give
my paper to Hawking?
아니
Sorry, I can't.
대체 왜?
What, why not?
3일 전에 이미 줬어
I gave it to him three days ago.
감명 받았대
He was really
impressed.
널 만나고 싶어하셔
He wants to meet you.
그러지 뭐
All right, then.
고마워, 하워드
Thank you, Howard.
호킹 교수님께 알려줘
Please let
Professor Hawking know
편한 시간에 만나자고
that I'm available
at his earliest convenience.
반응이 더
클 줄 알았는데
I thought he might be
a little more excited.
기다려봐
Give it a second.
(Sheldon whooping wildly)
호킹 교수님
Professor Hawking,
만나뵙게 되서 영광입니다
it's an honor and a privilege
to meet you, sir.
(beeping)
알고 있어
I know.
시간 내주셔서
감사합니다
I want to thank you for
taking time to see me.
(beeps)
나도 반갑네
My pleasure.
논문은 재밌게 읽었어
I enjoyed reading
your paper very much.
명석한 두뇌를 갖고 있더군
You clearly have
a brilliant mind.
알고 있어요
I know.
(beeping)
힉스 입자가 시간을 거슬러
올라가는 블랙홀이란 발상이 재밌네
Your thesis that the Higgs boson
is a black hole
accelerating backwards
through time is fascinating.
감사합니다
Thank you.
샤워를 하던 중에 떠올랐어요
It just-- it came to me
one morning in the shower.
(beeps)
그렇군
That's nice.
안타깝게도 잘못됐네
Too bad it's wrong.
무슨 말씀이세요?
What do you mean wrong?
(beeps)
2 페이지에 계산 실수가 있어
You made an arithmetic mistake
on page two.
(beeping)
어처구니 없더군
It was quite the boner.
그럴 리가요
No, no... that
can't be right.
계산 실수 따위는
하지 않아요
I-I don't make
arithmetic mistakes.
내 실수라는 말인가?
Are you saying I do?
아뇨
Oh, no,
물론 아니죠
no, no, of course not.
그러니까 제 말은...
It's just, I
was thinking...
이런, 실수를 했네
Oh, gosh, golly,
I made a boo-boo,
스티븐 호킹한테
보여주기까지 했어
and I gave it to
Stephen Hawking.
꼭 기절하는
녀석들이 있더라
Great, another fainter.
공대언니 블로그
http://tbbt.tistory.com
== sync, corrected by elderman ==